[{"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/尺子.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/圆珠笔.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/足球.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔4.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [0, 2, 2], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/毽子.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合2/卷笔刀.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/钢笔.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [1, 0, 1], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}], [{"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/帽衫.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_4.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔4.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_2.svg"}], [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/绿色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [4, 3, 0], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}], [{"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/跳绳.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/羽毛球.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/长裤_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/棒球棍.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/足球.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [2, 2, 2], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/尺子.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔4.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/网球拍1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}], [{"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/黄色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [4, 3, 0], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/圆珠笔.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/乒乓球拍.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合2/卷笔刀.svg"}], [{"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/蓝色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/黄色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/紫色裙子2.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [2, 3, 0], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/羽毛球.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔4.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [3, 1, 2], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L3.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/乒乓球拍.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔3.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合2/卷笔刀.svg"}], [{"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [3, 1, 4], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海豚_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}], [{"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/polo_2.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/衬衫.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/尺子.svg"}], [{"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [0, 4, 1], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L4.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/海马_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/棒球.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/夹克.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/网球拍1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/毽子.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/篮球.svg"}], [{"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [3, 1, 3], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}], [{"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裤_1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/桌球.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/羽毛球.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/毽子.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [2, 0, 0], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裤_1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/polo_2.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/帽衫.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/圆珠笔.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/绿色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [2, 4, 2], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔4.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/钢笔.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/桌球.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [4, 4, 4], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R5.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔1.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/篮球.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔4.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/钢笔.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [3, 1, 3], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/水母_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L2.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_R2.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "sportEquipment", "src": "v2/通用/体育/网球拍1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合2/卷笔刀.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔3.svg"}], [{"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_4.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_1.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_3.svg"}, {"type": "surface", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/手表_2.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [3, 1, 2], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/长颈鹿_L1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/绵羊_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}], [{"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔3.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/夹克.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/长裤_1.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [2, 2, 4], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "swim", "src": "v2/通用/动物/3-特殊分类_能游的/鱼_L6.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Left/狮子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/斑马_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/铅笔_3.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_1.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_4.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/polo_2.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/连衣裙_1.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/半裙组合_2/蓝色裙子2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [2, 0, 1], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}, {"body": [{"title": "分类选择", "stem": "选择一个和其他不是同类的", "selectType": "1", "content": [[{"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鸟_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜜蜂_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}], [{"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/袜子_2.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/T恤_4.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/衬衫.svg"}, {"type": "stationery", "src": "v2/通用/文具/文具组合1/笔2.svg"}, {"type": "clothing", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裤_1.svg"}], [{"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"}, {"type": "skirt", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/服装/短裙组合_1/短裙_2.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"}, {"type": "hat", "src": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"}]], "type": "au-classify-similar"}], "answers": [4, 3, 1], "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "分类", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-4-2-6"}]